<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ryuki Furukawaの自己紹介ページ on Hugoサンプル</title>
    <link>https://ryuki999.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ryuki Furukawaの自己紹介ページ on Hugoサンプル</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ryuki999.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multi-langue et i18n</title>
      <link>https://ryuki999.github.io/research/i18n/_index.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryuki999.github.io/research/i18n/_index.fr/</guid>
      <description>Learn est complètement compatible avec le mode multi-langue d&amp;rsquo;Hugo.
Il fournit :
 Des translation strings pour les valeurs par défaut utilisées par le thème (Anglais et Français). N&amp;rsquo;hésitez pas à contribuer ! Génération automatique du menu avec le contenu multi-langue Modification de la langue dans le navigateur  Configuration simple Après avoir appris comment Hugo gère les sites multi-langue, définissez vos langues dans votre fichier config.toml.
Par exemple, pour ce site, avec du contenu en français et en anglais.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attachments</title>
      <link>https://ryuki999.github.io/personal-history/attachments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryuki999.github.io/personal-history/attachments/</guid>
      <description>The Attachments shortcode displays a list of files attached to a page.
  Attachments   BachGavotteShort.mp3  (357 kb)   Carroll_AliceAuPaysDesMerveilles.pdf  (175 kb)   adivorciarsetoca00cape.pdf  (361 kb)   hugo.png  (17 kb)   movieselectricsheep-flock-244-32500-2.mp4  (340 kb)    Usage The shortcurt lists files found in a specific folder. Currently, it support two implementations for pages
  If your page is a markdown file, attachements must be placed in a folder named like your page and ending with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://ryuki999.github.io/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryuki999.github.io/credits/</guid>
      <description>Contributors Thanks to them for making Open Source Software a better place !
And a special thanks to @vjeantet for his work on docdock, a fork of hugo-theme-learn. v2.0.0 of this theme is inspired by his work.
Packages and libraries  mermaid - generation of diagram and flowchart from text in a similar manner as markdown font awesome - the iconic font and CSS framework jQuery - The Write Less, Do More, JavaScript Library lunr - Lunr enables you to provide a great search experience without the need for external, server-side, search services&amp;hellip; horsey - Progressive and customizable autocomplete component clipboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>https://ryuki999.github.io/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ryuki999.github.io/showcase/</guid>
      <description>TAT by OVH Tshark.dev by Ross Jacobs inteliver by Amir Lavasani </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
